// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
            "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following tag is used to mark the beginning of paragraph?",
        answer: "P",
        options: [
            "TD",
            "br",
            "P",
            "TR"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "From which tag descriptive list starts?",
        answer: "DL",
        options: [
            "LL",
            "DD",
            "DL",
            "DS"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Correct HTML Tag for the largest heading is?",
        answer: "h1",
        options: [
            "head",
            "h6",
            "heading",
            "h1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The attribute of form tag?",
        answer: "Both A and B",
        options: [
            "Method",
            "Action",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Markup tags tell the web browser?",
        answer: "How to display the page",
        options: [
            "How to organise the page",
            "How to display the page",
            "How to display message box on page",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "www is based on which model?",
        answer: "Client-server",
        options: [
            "Local-server",
            "Client-server",
            "3-tier",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What are Empty elements and is it valid?",
        answer: "Empty elements are element with no data",
        options: [
            "No, there is no such terms as Empty Element",
            "Empty elements are element with no data",
            "No, it is not valid to use Empty Element",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum chartacter?",
        answer: "maxlength",
        options: [
            "size",
            "len",
            "maxlength",
            "all of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Web pages starts with which of the follow tag?",
        answer: "HTML",
        options: [
            "Body",
            "Title",
            "HTML",
            "Form"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "HTML is a subset of",
        answer: "SGML",
        options: [
            "SGMT",
            "SGML",
            "SGMD",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Which of the following is a container?",
        answer: "Both a and b",
        options: [
            "SELECT",
            "BODY",
            "INPUT",
            "Both a and b"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "The attribute, which define the relationship between current document and HREF'ed URL is",
        answer: "REL",
        options: [
            "REL",
            "URL",
            "REV",
            "all of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "DT tag is desginer to fit a single line of our web page but DD tag will accept a",
        answer: "full paragraph",
        options: [
            "line of text",
            "full paragraph",
            "word",
            "request"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Character encoding is",
        answer: "a system that consists of a code which pairs each character with a pattern, sequence of natural numbers or electrical pulse in order to transmit the data",
        options: [
            "method used to represent numbers in a character",
            "method used to represent character in a number",
            "a system that consists of a code which pairs each character with a pattern, sequence of natural numbers or electrical pulse in order to transmit the data",
            "none of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "From which tag the descriptive list starts",
        answer: "DL",
        options: [
            "LL",
            "DD",
            "DL",
            "DS"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Correct HTML to left align the content inside a table cell is",
        answer: "td align = left",
        options: [
            "td left",
            "td raligh = left",
            "td align = left",
            "td leftalign"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "The tag which allows you to rest other HTML tags within the description is",
        answer: "CAPTION",
        options: [
            "TH",
            "TD",
            "TR",
            "CAPTION"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "BASE tag is designed to appear only between",
        answer: "HEAD",
        options: [
            "HEAD",
            "TITLE",
            "BODY",
            "FORM"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "How can you open a link in a new browser window?",
        answer: "a href = url target = _blank",
        options: [
            "a href = url target = new",
            "a href = url target _blank",
            "a href = url .new",
            "a href = url target = open"
        ]
    },
];